{
    "id": "50def8caabee4d168a5bbb15b44c5988",
    "title": "Underline the adjective clauses: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1c50d51796d24fe892cf068b98000dce",
            "title": "Adjective Clauses",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The girl ........................................ won the first prize is my niece.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The forest through ........................................... we travelled was dark and gloomy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My sister ............................................. lives in Mexico is a nurse.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the same house ......................................... Tennyson occupied.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "who",
                        "where"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the same old story .................................................. we have been hearing since our childhood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "what",
                        "that",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has a brilliant son .................................................... is certain to bring credit to his family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "All ................................................. glitters is not gold.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "what",
                        "which",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ................................................ is down fears no fall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "what",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The plan .................................................... I proposed was rejected.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the reason ................................................. he does not want to come here.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "why",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}